http://www.gqproduct.com/privacy.shtml

Privacy Policy - GQ RC Product
Login
Register
My Cart (0)
Privacy Policy
GQ protects the privacy of the individuals that visit our website. We recognize that we must maintain and use customer that information responsibly and we do not sell or rent the information you provide to us while visiting our website.
In future, if there are changes you will be notified before we use your information in a manner not previously disclosed in our privacy policy by posting the policy changes in this location or by communicating directly with you. As such, you will have the opportunity to opt out of any new use of your information.
Visitor can visit our website without identifying themself or sending us any personal information. While we do record their IP addresses when browsing different pages and remain anonymous, as we use this information to track the popular pages viewed.
When you register to become GQ member on-line, we receive personal information from you such as  your name, e-mail addresses, telephone number,mailing address, credit card information, etc. From time to time, you will receive e-mails from us regarding our products, services, and promotions.
We do not sell, rent or share the information that you provide to us to the third parties other than internal use only .
We allow cookie to store inside the temporary file of your computer while you can delete if need be.
GQ website reserves the right to modify or supplement this statement at any time without prior notice.
If you have question regarding our privacy policies, please e-mail us at gqrcproduct@hotmail.com
© 2020 GQ RC Product. All Rights Reserved.
